[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many hours of sleep do sloths normally need per day?", "correct_answer": "Less than 10 hours", "incorrect_answers": ["20-22 hours", "12-13 hours", "15-18 hours"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which continent does the turtle-dove migrate to in the colder winter months?", "correct_answer": "Africa", "incorrect_answers": ["Australia", "North America", "Asia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What Hollywood actress starred in the 1942 film Casablanca, ranked the second best movie of all time by the American Film Institute?", "correct_answer": "Ingrid Bergman", "incorrect_answers": ["Greta Garbo", "Katharine Hepburn", "Audrey Hepburn"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The story of Atlantis dates all the way back to ancient Egypt. The story was first written down by the traveller Solon. But who wrote the only remaining story of the lost continent Atlantis?", "correct_answer": "Plato", "incorrect_answers": ["Aristotle", "Christopher Columbus", "Socrates"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The acetic acid, the acetylene and the ethene have an equal number of this atom in their molecules.", "correct_answer": "C", "incorrect_answers": ["H", "Fe", "O"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "About how many lightning bolts strike the Earth each second?", "correct_answer": "100", "incorrect_answers": ["1,500", "1,000", "3,000"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Although not all bear subspecies are vicious, there is a tendency for increase in bear attacks due to this factor.", "correct_answer": "Destruction of bears natural habitat", "incorrect_answers": ["Pollution", "Genetical mutation of bears", "Hunting"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "SMERSH, the organization mentioned in the James Bond film, From Russia with Love, was a real Russian organization.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 1967, Egypt effectively blockaded Eilat by closing this area to Israel.", "correct_answer": "The Straits of Tiran", "incorrect_answers": ["The Golan Heights", "The Sinai Peninsula", "The Suez Canal"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This is the microscope part in which the lens is located.", "correct_answer": "Ocular or eyepiece", "incorrect_answers": ["Objectives", "Body tube", "Mirror"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What female rapper plays one of Carmens best friends in the movie Carmen: A Hip Hopera?", "correct_answer": "Rah Digga", "incorrect_answers": ["Da Brat", "Lil Kim", "Trina"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who was Robert Van Winkle ?", "correct_answer": "Vanilla Ice", "incorrect_answers": ["A fictional character who slept for many years", "Ice-T", "The first winner of the Congressional  Medal of Honor"]}]